Guide to the Judith P. Vladeck Papers WAG.177
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory, 1
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Proceedings (?), May 27, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Proceedings (?), Sep 21, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Deposition Upon Oral Examination of Paul Zweier, May 4, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Stipulation of Settlement, May 20, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Structural A (1st Mandamus) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Kyriazi- Summaries of Trial Transcripts (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Stage II Proceedings/Distribution: Structural XV- Book I- O-O-I (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Employee Rate Cards #0009-#0194 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Employee Rate Cards #0201-#0461/ #2072-#3215 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Employee Rate Cards #4003-7226 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Employee Rate Cards Unnumbered in Alphabetical Order (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: JPV & JLB Settlement Notes, Aug-Sep 1983 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Claim Form Problems (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Main-Hurdman Report (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: K. Berylson Deposition Transcript (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Content of Notice- Attorneys Fees/Research (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Manual for Complex Litigation/Research (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi- Prep. For Brief (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Affidavit as to Mailing of Notice Paragraph 3(B)- Inactive Employees- 475-73 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Affidavit as to Mailing of Notice Paragraph 3(C) and 3(D)- Priority Hire Lists-475-73 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Plant Closing Appeal- Joint Appendix (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Diaries (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Plant Closing Appeal- Research (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Research Modification of Consent Degree (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi 1983 Western Electric AACP (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Settlement Notes and Drafts (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Transcripts and Notes of Hearings (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 10K- AT&T (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: AT&T Annual Report, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Appeal RE: Plant Closing Orders/ Docket No. 83-5353 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - WE: Board Minutes & Executive Committee Minutes ~1847 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Letter: RE: Kearnys Divisional Alignment ~1840, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Kearny Forecasts ~1808, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Employee Benefits Survey ~ 1738, Jun 2, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Layoff Casts by Location ~1739, Jun 2, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Covey to Chittick undated Letter ~1850, Jun 2, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - WE Co. Total Company Gross Payroll ~1849 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Employees and Payroll ~1848 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Kearny MPF, Book 1, Section 3 ~1838 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Forecasts- Indexes Only ~1841 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Electronic Components Division and Common Technology ~1839 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Documents to Use (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Photocopies of Case Rulings (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Contempt/Consent Decrees (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Folder ~1788 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Waiver ~1882 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Search for and Production of Documents from 6/6/80-2/18/83 Concerning the Impact of the Kearny AAP on Other WE Facilities and or Impact of Intended Phaseout of Kearny Operations on Kearny AAP. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - New Interrogatory Requests (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Relevant Data as to Male Hire (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Appendix to Sixth Interim Report on Computation of Credits to be Used in Distribution of Settlement Fund- Volume 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Appendix to Fifth Interim Report on Computation of Credits to be Used in Distribution of Settlement Fund- Volume 1 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Appendix to Fifth Interim Report on Computation of Credits to be Used in Distribution of Settlement Fund- Volume 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi Telephone Logs And Distribution (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Notes (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Copies of Womens letters A-C, May-Aug 1981 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Copies of Womens letters D-G, May-Aug 1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Copies of Womens letters H-K, May-Aug 1981 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Copies of Womens letters L-O, May-Aug 1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Copies of Womens letters P-S, May-Aug 1981 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Copies of Womens letters T-Z, May-Aug 1981 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi Interoffice & Others: Requests for Rulings and Applications (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi Interoffice & Others: Applicant Schedules (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Stage II Statistics, Schedules (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Stage II- Legal (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Notes (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi Status Conference (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Stage II Rulings (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Kyriazi- Court and Master Rulings (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Stage II Interoffice Memos (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Notice to Class Interrogatories (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Proof (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - WE Organizational Chart (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Testing- WE Tests & When Given (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Kyriazi II- Scheduling (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Kyriazi II- InterOffice Memoranda through 8/31/1979, Aug 31, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi II- Correspondence, Sep 1, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi Legal Correspondence (General), Sep 1-Nov 5, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Notes/Misc. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi II- InterOffice Memoranda through 8/31/1979, Aug 31, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi II- Correspondence, Sep 1, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Research Folder (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Tax File (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Chronological Tax File, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Extra Copies (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Tax File- Structural I (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric Third Circuit Appeal- Transcript of Settlement Hearing Before Judge Stern, Jan 22, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric- Third Circuit Appeal- Brief and Reply of Oliver Lofton, Esq.: Atty for Petitioners- Appellants (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Blue Binder: Our Brief/ WEs Brief (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric- Third Circuit Appeal- Brief of JPV and Fortunato Brief, Nov 20-21, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Extra Copies Appellate Documents (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Extra Papers- First Mandamus Kyriazi O-43h (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Extra Papers- Second Mandamus Kyriazi O-43i (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Correspondence, Jan 1982 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Extra Papers- Third Mandamus Kyriazi O-43j (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Cleos Papers: Exhibits RE: Kyriazis Individual Claim (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi Current (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Settlement Structural: Proposals and Notes: Plaintiffs & Defendants Proposals- Structural VI (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Settlement Structural: Proposals and Notes: Settlement Hearing, Jul 24, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Settlement Structural: Proposals and Notes: Drafts- Affirmative Action Program (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Settlement Structural: Proposals and Notes: Notes (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Settlement Structural: Proposals and Notes: Plaintiffs Affirmative Action Program (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Settlement Structural: Proposals and Notes: Defendants Response to Plaintiffs Proposed Settlement Agreement (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Settlement Structural: Proposals and Notes: Transcripts (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Settlement Structural: Proposals and Notes: Originals (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Settlement Structural: Proposals and Notes: Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Settlement Structural: Proposals and Notes: Proposed Final Orders of Settlement- Drafts (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Small Copies of Blow-ups (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - 63- Original Charts (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - 13-Extra Color Copies (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Claims of Denial of Opportunity: Sheila Guszowski (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Claims of Denial of Opportunity: Gladys Doe (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Claims of Denial of Opportunity: Notes and Memoranda (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Claims of Denial of Opportunity: Blank Forms (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Claims of Denial of Opportunity: Delores Dunn (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Claims of Denial of Opportunity: Ada Johnson (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Claims of Denial of Opportunity: Class-Wide (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Claims of Denial of Opportunity: Ruth Taylor (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Claims of Denial of Opportunity: Millicent Wright (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Claims of Denial of Opportunity: Kyriazi Monitoring- Memoranda & Notes (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Monitering Structural (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi folder/ Kyriazi Checks (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Interrogatory Copies (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Returned Letters to Class Members, Jan 4, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi Settlement Files [Extra copies from Danny Engelstein for JPVs use] (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi: Job Posting, Mar 1981 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: DistributionNotes and InterOffice (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Aug 1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Legal Correspondence/Class Member Correspondence, Oct 1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: MonitoringNotes and InterOffice (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Class Member Correspondence, Sep 1981 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Legal Correspondence, Sep 1981 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Nov 1981 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Class Member Correspondence, Nov 1981 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Publicity (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Oct 1981 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Jul 1981 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Jun 1981 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, May 1981 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Proposed Findings and Conclusions (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Copies: Post-Settlement Structural- Valerie Martilly (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Rejected Applicant Copies (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Brief in Opposition to Defendants Motion to Dismiss Claims Against Individual Defendants (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Extra Copy- Appendix to Plaintiffs Proposed Findings of Fact Regarding Computation of Damages to Plaintiff Kyriazi (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Settlement Agreement (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Stipulation of Settlement (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Structural E- Volume II: Cleos Individual Claim (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi Form Files (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi Class Exhibits (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: RE: Adie v. Western Electric- 9th/ Civil Action No. 72-1352/ Our File No. 7000126 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi Monitoring: Notes on Layoffs (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi Monitoring: Mailings to Class- lists, letters, etc. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Correspondence, Jan-May 1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Correspondence, Jun-Dec 1982 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Class Cards and Returned Mailings (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Brief of Plaintiff-Appellee (2 copies) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Extra- Opinion of Judge Stern After Distribution (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Class Member Objections/Comments to Proposed Formula (#1-3) (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Record of Telephone Calls (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Fifth Report of Computation of Credits to be Used in Distribution of Settlement Fund #5 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Fourth Interim Report of Computation of Credits to be Used in Distribution of Settlement Fund #6 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Second Interim Report of Computation of Credits to be Used in Distribution of Settlement Fund #7 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: First Interim Report of Computation of Credits to be Used in Distrubution of Settlement Fund #8 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Third Interim Report of Computation of Credits to be Used in Distribution of Settlement Fund #9 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Returned Enveloped from October 1984 Mailing, Oct 1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts of Hearings for retirees #11, Jan 16-17, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Report of Special Master on the Hearings for retirees #11 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Hearing #12, Mar 18, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Objections to 1983 Settlement #13 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 7-193 Claim of Joyce Gardinella #14 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 7-193 Claim of Elizabeth N. Fox #15 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 7-193 Kyriazi- Extra Copies of Papers Relating to Distribution of the 1984 Fund #16 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Helen Stellinus (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Elizabeth M. Causby (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Elizabeth Janowski (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Immacolata R. Maranto (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Anne Toomey (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Lorraine T. Szaro (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Caroline A. Plesniarski (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Katharina Strother Carls (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Mary Zadrozny (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Antoinette M. Serio (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Dorothy H. Angermeyer (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Gloria A. Whalen (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Lillian E. Greene (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Magdalena Americk (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Anna R. Solecki (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Rita M. Allen (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Eleanore M. Cavallo (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Agnes H. Pasko (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Anne Mados (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Anna Slapar (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Madeline M. Comerie (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Julia L. Wilkerson (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Marie C. Fitzsimmons (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Sabina G. Stephen (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Viola Holgate (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Jennie Procopio (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Carmela M. Raspantini (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Eva M. Lempicki (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Kathryne E. Jeranek (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Mary Marton (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Florence B. Kaminski (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Clara Stiller (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Mary Varchula (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Hedwig M. Dulski (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Alma D. Fiume (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Helen J. Maciaszek (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Ann Gentiluomo (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Kyriazi Retiree Hearing Files #17: Dorothy Evans (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Structural work #18 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: #19: Attorneys Fees Structural I (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: #19: Status Conference Transcripts RE: Attorneys fees (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: #19: Hours & Disbursements, Stage I, Stage II and Distribution- Dannys Notes (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Kyriazi Stage II Attorneys Fees #19 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Kyriazi Attorneys Fees- Stipulation of Settlement #19 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Motion to Modify Consent Decree Structural Vol. I (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Structural III Rule 23 Motion (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Structural IV (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Plaintiffs Memorandum to Special Master Thomas F. Campion W/Exhibits, Jul 8, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Notes in Maroon Binder (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Draft-Objections (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi Monitoring- Denial of Opportunity (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric:- Distribution, Open Items (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Denial of Opportunity of Claim- Dorothy Gray (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Denial of Opportunity of Claim-Camille Foti (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Denial of Opportunity of Claim-Peggy Ann Salters (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Denial of Opportunity of Claim- General, Background, Potential (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Monitoring: Jeanette Scott & Thelma Chapman (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Monitoring File (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Misc. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Layoff Docket (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Hearings Before Special Master Goldstein (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi- Address Changes and Telephone Numbers list Address List, Feb 1985 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - WE- Original 7/27 & 10/29 Class Member Letters (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Notes of Meetings, Aug 12-15, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Notes of Meeting, Mar 15, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Status Conference on Computerization, Aug 27, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Status Conference on Computerization, Sep 20, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Status Conference on Computerization, Sep 20, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Status Conference on Computerization, Sep 24, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Status Conference on Computerization, Sep 24, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Status Conference on Computerization, Oct 3, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Status Conference on Computerization, Oct 4, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Status Conference on Computerization, Oct 22, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Stage II Computerization Status Conference Transcripts- Preliminary Matters, Mar 6, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Stage II Computerization Status Conference Transcripts- Preliminary Matters, May 14, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Stage II Computerization Status Conference Transcripts- Volume I pp.1-139, Jul 24, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Stage II Computerization Status Conference Transcripts- Volume II pp. 140-226, Jul 31, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Stage II Computerization Status Conference Transcripts- Volume III pp. 228-360, Aug 2, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Stage II Computerization Status Conference Transcripts- 08/09/1979- Volume IV pp. 361-500, Aug 9, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Stage II Computerization Status Conference Transcripts- Volume V pp. 501-593, Aug 27, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Deposition of Donald E. Geis- Volume I, May 9, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Deposition of Donald E. Geis-Continued Depo. (2), Jun 3, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Deposition of William B. Marx, Jr.- Volume II (2), May 10, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Deposition of William B. Marx, Jr.- Continued Depo. (2), Jun 3, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Deposition of James Joseph Meenan- Vol. 3 Pg. 3.45, May 17, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Deposition of Dale Jones- Vol. 3 Pg. 3.77, May 17, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Deposition of Paul Zweier-Vol. 4 Pg. 4.1, May 24, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Deposition of Thaddeus J. Szymczak- Vol. 4 Pg. 4.119 (2), May 24, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Deposition of John A. Heck- Vol. 4 Pg. 4.78 (2), May 24, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Deposition of John M. Brown- Vol. 5 Pg. 5.121 (2), May 25, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Deposition of Roland Boyd Butterfield- Vol. 5 Pg. 5.1 (3), May 25, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Deposition of Joe Ramirez- Vol. 5 Pg. 5.159 (2), May 25, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Deposition of Joe Ramirez- Vol. 5 Pg. 5.199 (2), May 27, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Deposition of Eugene Joseph Eckel- Vol. 6 Pg. 6.1 (2), May 26, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Deposition of Donald E. Procknow- Vol. 1 Pg. 1.205 (2), Jun 3, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Deposition of Donald E. Procknow- Vol. I, May 9, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Deposition of George v. Cook- Vol. 7 Pg. 7.1 (2), Jun 3, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Deposition of Andrew J. Davis- Vol. 8 Pg. 8.1 (2), Jun 8, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Deposition of Andrew J. Davis- Vol. 8 Pg. 8.117 (2), Jun 21, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Order, Jun 3, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Hearing on Defendants Objections to Second Request for Production of Documents (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Deposition Exhibits- Paul Zweier (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Deposition Exhibits- Eugene Eckel (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Deposition Exhibits- John Heck (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Deposition Exhibits- John Brown (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Deposition Exhibits- Donald Geis (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Deposition Exhibits- James Meehan (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Deposition Exhibits- Donald Procknow (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Deposition Exhibits- Ramirez (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Deposition Exhibits- Butterfield (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Deposition Exhibits- Andrew Davis (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Deposition Exhibits- George Cook (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Kyriazi II Wanda Altmajer- B16-2177: Claim form (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi II Wanda Altmajer- B16-2177: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi II Wanda Altmajer- B16-2177: Interrogatories (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi II Wanda Altmajer- B16-2177: Notes (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi II Wanda Altmajer- B16-2177: Exhibits (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi II Wanda Altmajer- B16-2177: Transcripts (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi II- Lutrecia Gould- TFC-2412: Claim form (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi II- Lutrecia Gould- TFC-2412: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi II- Lutrecia Gould- TFC-2412: Interrogatories (Box 27, Folder 9)